They said the gods were gone
But we build new ones in code and song
Every follower, a priest, every troll
Seals on the Colts great door
One for truth
Hear the choir of lost accounts, their laughed accounts, their silenced mouths
Each band of baptism each strike a scar, but the cold wind
Log in, beloved. Take your roll.
For every cold begins with one.
When the static
Is it plugged in? What's going on?
You hear me? Someone join here.
it dropped the camera unfortunately um so hopefully it didn't break or something i don't
know let me check hold on i might have to come back in one second
I'm just a little bit groggy.
Just do my green screen, green screen, huh?
Okay.
Oh, my hair is getting long, huh?
Oh, anyone wanna come up?
I know it's like very early in the morning.
I was up, I was up, so.
go on for a little bit yeah it was emotional day yesterday but i was gonna say the worst part
about it was like i had sent like a text message the other day day before yesterday or something
like that trying to explain exactly what had upset me but it's like that person took it the
Being a soccer or something like I don't know it wasn't I wasn't talking about them. I was talking about
I was talking about
My life experience and like what my associations and things like that was not talking about them at all
I know the person's not Russian, right?
Whatever it said, right?
But they took it the wrong way but it's okay, it's not okay, but I think I
Probably like I just look stupid trying to keep explaining
So it's just frustrating misunderstandings
Also, I don't know if I guess be like forgets. Oh, yeah, like this is the other person the beat-up forgets
Like what she says to me
Or she calls me when she's like so drunk and like mean
And then the next day she wakes up, sovers up and just like watches my show or something like that and then
It's triggered again because I was upset about what she said and then she accuses me of
Calling her names and stuff like that. It's like I
Did but I did it in response to it's just like
constant
I'll say it's probably all my fault, you know, it's like because I'm not the best communicator. I'm not very good at relationships or
any of that
Which is probably why I'm like, you know alone, but
We're like to be alone
I don't know I don't mean any harm to anybody and it's like I'm definitely not like
this
Machiavelli and
Spen golly type like that. I'm painted out as at all like I
But it's like I guess they always I get along me
It's my it's like the authority Capricorns have and they this is it or this natural like kind of authority or some people like
How are we doing in chat today
I think Bea is upset with you for joining your panel.
Whoa, wow, Daryl, I mean, it's like, that's,
hey, Ivana, how are you?
I mean, what, she's gonna be mad about people joining,
am I mad about it?
Am I allowed to be mad at people joining her panel?
Or her, I mean, it's like, how dare she,
how dare she get mad at anybody?
And it's like, I know it's like,
I mean, I don't get mad at anybody for joining her panel
as much as people try to paint it and stuff.
Good morning, Ivana.
like Flirty Diamond was like a few weeks ago on her panel saying oh well I got unmodded from Psyche's because
I was on your panel beta in a second that I wrote story diamond and then I was like on Instagram
I said I didn't kick in unmod you because you're on beta's panel. Like it's like it just makes me look like some kind of petty jerk or whatever
And I actually I didn't do that at all and then she like tells oh, he's writing me on SAP
Oh, he's over on Instagram. He's watching like and it's just like oh god. It's like
more misunderstandings and so
Yeah, I don't know it's like I mean that's why it's like I guess I guess it's important if you have the chance to like
You know talk it out as soon as possible, which is my mistake, which I didn't do
I know or you know in one of the situations and then if you let even one day go by it's like
you know
It looks really bad on me, I guess but I'm hey, hey Rudy. How are you?
But I wasn't trying to like
Accuses anybody of anything or I don't know
It's very misunderstood
I'm not trying to like it sympathy. I mean, it's like what I don't have me
It's just like I'm just like emotionally redrained right now
Over it because it's like plus it's like, you know Christmas time and it's like I feel like maybe it's like if there's any time
To be like a little like, you know, just like to take a step back or be forgiven
I know it's like a few people are under a lot of stress right now and stuff
It'd be like, you know, maybe like wrong Christmas time, but
You know, maybe I'm asking too much
and so that's that but how are you guys I'm still sick a little bit I have a
cough and yeah I have a cough I was just gonna be I'm just gonna see maybe I'll
have this like cold coffee and like
Finish up or maybe I just I did kind of a sleep stream for like a little bit yesterday
And I was like you know there's people in chat like I'd like to talk and hang out
But it looks like there's not too many people here right now, but
I'm just sorry if I did something wrong, which I did just like this by not communicating well
I like sabotage myself. I ruin like
That's not terrible. Yeah, the cat was playing with the mouse earlier
I don't know. There's a lot of mice outside right now
The cats are just having so much fun going out and catching and playing with these little mice
But it's like bodies laying over on the floor over there. I want to step on it be so gross
I don't think I've ever stepped on like a dead mouse, but hey, reality Nancy. How are you?
You came from a stay turns channel. It's new. Oh, that's good
Hope he's doing good. I was on LES's channel and LES is it was like, you know, it's lower east side
And he treated me really really really nicely and really well
unfortunately ghost
Who was the one who asked me if I would go on the panel and stuff?
Started to like be abusive and I just like left but I don't know what his problem is like why he has to like say
I'm like I'm the stupidest person in the world and there's like an idiot and
But I guess that's our dynamic now
Just unfortunate hey
We're there already hey, Amanda, how are you?
There's mr. Rudy. I'll turn off my background cuz it's so he's so cute right now
They hope you did like that my new music video that I made
Yeah, mostly draining and it's like and they're just like and then it's like just misunderstood too because it's like I
Totally I try to fix things, you know, and it's like I should and I should probably like not like I should probably like leave him
Leave things be for a second or I should have like, you know
been quicker with it or whatever
but um, I
Don't know. I'm just I'm always a bad guy, right?
Yeah, mr. Root. Hey, how are you?
Your ear itches. Hey
You pay your ear
And where's tricks it's tricks up there tricks is right there. Oh, hi
Hi, what are you doing?
Mr. Tricks
Tix and Rudy
There's Lenore Lenore around haven't seen Lenore and Lola was in here playing with a mouse earlier
It's kind of gross. I think it's dead, but you just have to throw it tossing it around in the air and stuff
Yeah, but I mean I am kind of happy about a few things like I get to buy my
nieces and nephews like at least at least seven of them like like the seven
like little kids like a few of my brothers and sisters had like you know
kids like under 10 years old and so I get them pretty much Christmas presents
but it's like there's so many people in my family if I was to get my brother's
sisters all my nieces and nephews gifts would be like 40 gifts and it's like a
little bit overwhelming so I think seven's a good amount
to stick to just make sure all the little kids get a gift and maybe if I have a little extra I'll
get something from my sister but nobody gets me gifts anymore though you know it's like
I think like last year my sister got me a toothbrush like an electric toothbrush
and then my mom got me like a gift card for the pet store you know but uh
I think that I've probably gone for so many years of not kidding people gifts that it's like, you know
I'm not not saying I should be getting gifts. I mean, it's just like but it is a gift to be able to you know
have friends on YouTube though and
Have a show on YouTube still going and it's like that's exciting
Yeah, you know, yeah
So you can see the cats there's mr. Rude like the background you got the green screen right there already
Green screen looks really good today, huh?
Yeah, are you good?
And you're good tricks. Are you good tricks?
Where are you?
Hi.
Can I pet your butt?
Oh, pet your butt.
Yeah, Lenore left him on the keyboard.
I heard Sandman was playing that clip.
I don't know if they were like saying,
Oh, he's sort of like, they keep trying to say it's so disgusting
that like my cats like have mice and stuff.
Like, I mean, that's what cats do.
There's the reason we had a plague in in like, you know, England or whatever and like the 1400s was because
they like the Vatican or something said that cats were like the devil and
People were killing the cats and then there was an out-of-control flea problem and the fleas carried
Plague right and so it's like so like so the cats are like these natural that they're adapted to like eat
Animals and like little mice and stuff like that. I know it's like can be gross and
It's like the thought of it is like oh they're eating bones and stuff
But they they get high on the brain like Paige explained it
She said they eat the brain and they get like a psychedelic
Kind of like high from eating the brain. You'll see them like rolling around sometimes after they get real playful and stuff
hey, dude and
Well Rudy is like Rudy is so soft. You're still such a soft cat, you know bring so it's an old man
He's such a soft little cat and he's a very sweet cat
Yeah
Yeah, so
But I was trying to explain to somebody about cats like cats in Russia
the cats are called the criminals, right?
And so that's like the nickname for criminals as a cat.
Like in things like that,
I was trying to explain that to somebody
and they thought that I was calling them
like a Russian criminal or something like that.
So which I wasn't doing,
I was trying to explain like something else, but.
I don't know just part of the misunderstanding that I'm talking about right now like that. There's misunderstandings
Hey, Lola. Oh, there's Lola Lola. What'd you do? Where's the where's the mouse Lola? Where's the mouse you brought in?
Do you leave it in the house or you took it outside? Oh, there she is. Oh
It's over there. Look at look. I must be still alive because she's like going under the
Oh my god, what if I pull back that thing and there's a dead mouse and it's gonna be so gross
I don't know if she like it's hiding under there or something. Yeah
Yeah, I've on it. So, you know, about that like that, like so I was trying to explain that to somebody like and tell them that I wasn't wasn't like
Their fault. I was triggered. It's like it's my fault, you know
It's like because I guess I have these different associations in my mind
But then they thought I was talking about them and now it's like I've over explained it so many times that it's like I just sound like
Desperate or like, you know clingy or something or needy or something and now it's like, oh, I should just like but it's a misunderstanding
And I feel like I should just address it
Especially since the person has already publicly addressed it like about me
So I guess I'll just do it here instead of like trying to explain again, but I wasn't talking about them
I was talking about my own fucked up mind and why I'm
Try it triggered and like mind-bucked and stuff. Oh, you're from a little bird to the front door here outside
You're after cat brought a bird to the front door that my cats used to bring these little songbirds bluebirds and like
There's been a squirrel in my house before actually possums moved in under my couch
Don't anybody hear this because they're gonna say oh my god. You're so disgusting possums
But yeah, these baby possums came in the house
They followed the mama in and then they would go out at night eat the cat food
They were there for a few days probably a weekend and stuff and I was getting my couch
Replaced anyway, and so as soon as they took out the couch these possums ran out
And
Yeah, it's kind of gross, you know, it's a little bit gross that I you know
You know to clean it up and
Yeah, there's some baby possums that you know
I wouldn't recommend having baby possums live in your house because they don't they don't know how to use the litter box
You know they don't have to use the litter box. Oh, you like that Rudy like that when I rub your rub your chin like that
Mr. Rudy so sweet. Oh, Mr. Roode
Little bumps. Hey, baby, you little bumps you little old man
Good cat, huh?
You good cat
He likes to sit up here. You can't with me. I know I know it's it's embarrassing
Then it's like this will be clipped and it's like oh my god. He had possums living in his house
I know and just like I had a squirrel once come in
When I go outside, I have like birds fly. It's like snow white
You know how snow white has like little birds coming to her finger and they're all like butterflies fly in front of me
Squirrels start going up the trees and stuff like I'm like I really do have like an energy
I think the animals respond to
So maybe because I'm just like loving or something like you don't have a doggy door
Yeah, I have a cat door and so they bring in like little mice and stuff
And then they showed the rest of the cats now the cats get excited
And if you saw like the mouse Lenore brought it in the other night
And she dropped on my keyboard when I was like sitting right here
She came up here and she had her mouth and then like it got clipped I guess and
It's funny and it is funny. It is funny, but it's like, you know, I
Do try to either save the mouse, you know, yeah, I try to save the mice
If I can if they're and I don't I can't stand if they squeak if they're like squeaky inside because it's just like it
It's like oh, they're like being tortured and stuff and I just feel bad
So I've saved a few I go put them on the hedge outside. I'm like, okay
Well, this is like the most I can do for you get the pen for yourself if they're dead
I've just put them in the trash bag and I put it in the dumpster and stuff
And I just hope that they're all the all the way dead and stuff, you know, it's like it's hard, you know
And once I'm on Leviathan told me, she's like, I was like, oh, you know, I try to save the mice.
She's like, don't, she's like, don't don't try to save them.
Just like, let nature take its course, you know, and she's like, you know, she's, she was very cold about it.
Right. Yeah, they bring me stuff out of respect that I've like, they think that it's like a nice treat and stuff like that.
They don't, you know, and I react, they go, ah, this is a big reaction.
And I think it's like something exciting and I'm happy.
But I kind of like grossed out a little bit.
I don't like.
I don't like dealing with dead animals, of course, I don't think anybody does, right?
So, I don't know. Dead bodies. Like, my dad once found a SUIC IDE victim who unalived himself at these clips nearby our house.
My dad used to walk...
He used to walk the dog.
Every day and so he found like a body of somebody once and then another time he like
The dog went down to this little ravine and my dad like went down followed him to the ravine and got him
But he couldn't hold the dog and climb up and so he had to be helicoptered out of this ravine
Cross the street from our house. I'm sorry. I sound really bad
Try to drink this coffee
I didn't see it in eggs was it like insulting to me because I know he's like
He gets to get insulting now. There's all these people saying oh, I have most disgusting carpet and oh
The only person who's carpet is worse than my it's good times because good times uses a lawnmower
To like you know in the darker first carpet or something like that
My carpet is honestly I have a vacuum cleaner right here. I mean I say I vacuum like kind of a bit
And this is actually a nice not a bad vacuum cleaner. So what is it Eureka?
Used to have a Dyson had a nice Dyson where my friend brought me one time and that lasted until like I destroyed it, you know
Excuse me, I know that sounds disgusting. He's at war with me. Okay. Well good
You think I care that guy's such an imbecile anyway
So good time to beer cans all over the floor etc. Well, it's like then I say I mentioned a picture of my floor
Which is like it was like a zoomed in it's like when the camera falls. It is a 4k
Webcam so it's very clear and it's like even if you look down on the floor
There's like a little bit of tobacco and people might say oh my god. It's so bad
But it's like that's like my floor. It's like a little bit like tobacco and like there's like a dime right there
There's like little pieces of tobacco of paper because I cut up these like fucking
cigars because
buying a cigar I can get a two pack of cigars for two dollars and uh and a pack of cigarettes is like
ten and twelve dollars and stuff like that what are you doing excuse me hello and so um I use these
cigars and so it's kind of messy right oh my god if Sam ends here oh my god speak of the devil
I can't even with the mouse yeah well the cat's like mice what like what have you heard of a cat
they're mortal enemies right? It's not like Ganesha. Ganesha, his mouse is like his vehicle.
So the elephant like rides the mouse in India right? And then it's like other places the
elephants are afraid of mice. But Ganesha rides the mouse. And this is Lola and she's like a
little hunter right? She's just a hunter. Do you see how wild she looks? She's from the streets
you know? She got picked up off the streets as a kitten. Yeah.
So it's like Tom and Jerry that's your little mouse and she'd like to throw in the air and then maybe bite off its head, right?
You don't mean to you're just playing right?
That's why I was trying to tell beat us the cats are like psychopaths because they like to play with their prey
But it's like cats really they don't really like you know, they see it more as play
They don't see that they're hurting it. They kind of like it's disappointed when I stop squeaking
It's kind of like oh the toy broke, you know, because they kind of think of it as like a little toy or something like that
Hi, baby my little baby. It's my sweetheart. Oh, you're a sweetheart. Oh, oh
Oh, you sweetheart. Oh, oh, oh, you like it, you like it, you like it. Yeah, oh, you like it. Yeah.
It's her little squeaky toy, right? So she don't mean it, but she got bored because it would stop
squeaky, right? But I think it's still alive because I don't see it over there, so I have to pull back my...
I think tomorrow, and look, where did you leave them?
You get the mouse under the table?
Did you throw it there, or is there a run over there?
I need to figure it.
I don't hear it squeaking, so that's a good sign,
but I don't want it to be like in the house, you know?
It's kinda gross.
I do like to save them as much as I can, right?
Oh, you like that?
Oh, oh, you love it.
Oh, you like when I rub your face.
Oh, you're so sweet.
You're so sweet, my little sweetheart.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, like that. Oh, oh, like that. Like that. Oh
Yeah, you like that, huh?
You're there already
We're here you're there. You're why are you why you're looking away? You're looking you're you're facing the opposite direction
You're going to link? Oh
She's purring
You're purring so sweet my little baby
They give you a professional massage like that you like that I go down. Oh is it good
You like that baby
Like I said when like Lola has the most beautiful eyes too if you can see her her like eyes are like so crystalline like green blue
Yeah, she's gorgeous, all gorgeous cats.
I have the best looking cats, I think, you know?
But they are very happy cats.
You can see they would not be like
just all sitting around like each other
because of the tricks up there.
Okay, well, let's see how this goes.
Hello.
You know nigga, that was a rat. Come on site. That was a little that was a mouse. It was a white little no little mouse
Big rat. It was a tiny
Don't drop it. No, no, no, not on my keyboard
Not on my keyboard. Yeah
Sike gotta feed them cats, man. Come on site. Hey, that was a big-ass rat. It's like that was a rat site
Nor she's like a rat. So that was a wrap
Play though. It was around side. They get they go outside. They like to play now. That was a rat
She was like a little brought in one tonight
And so they they're just like, you know, like to play with it. I guess there's a lot out right now for this
It was nothing that's right, like a big rats are like, you know, we're small
Well, it was what would you do you would probably make the same sound
Nah, nigga, I don't got rats in my house.
I don't have them in my house.
They're come from outside.
No, no, no, I think you got ready to eat.
You don't got ready to eat?
No, like I said, my carpet has tobacco
and it has the rolling pin.
You ever heard of ready to eat?
Yeah, it's an animated Disney movie where they had a crack.
Nah, that's the rule.
Not too ready to eat.
Come on.
No, it's not.
There's no rats in here.
They've got inside.
No, that's a big ass rat.
Oh my god.
The rat was so big, it was alive still.
You ain't going to kill me.
The cat didn't even kill it was so big.
It wasn't even big.
It was a small-
Man, look how I don't got the clip on that.
Well, you did.
Didn't you play it tonight on your show?
Yeah, it was on your live.
You didn't even delete your live.
I know.
Well, I'm ashamed or something
that my cats kind of mess.
I was proud.
Last time you were ashamed, you deleted it.
Well, I didn't.
Not because of that.
Like, seriously, it's like, well, I have to delete.
Were you yelling at me, man?
I feel uncomfortable.
Why are you yelling at me?
It's too early.
My voice is too early, Sight.
Why are you so aggressive with me, sir?
This is yelling at you.
No, this is just a normal voice.
Sir, why are you yelling at me, sir?
Come in peace.
I know, I know, I know.
I thought you said you were at war with me, though.
War?
Sight, you came at war with a fucking rat in your crib.
I came at war with you, though, and you're a rat.
What?
You're looking at me.
You lost, you lost, you lost.
You lost all your, all your, all your, all your heavy hitters.
Alex has gone for me.
Well, Alice Alice just misunderstood
What you got now who you got who's your who's your shooters now?
I don't I don't give away my donators because I don't want my donators to be harassed and
Shooters I just said donators. Come on. I don't care who you donate to who donate to you site. I don't care
My own shooter. I'm a Jamie's Cowboys. She's like this. Yeah, Jamie Cowboys. All right
So I go go to Jamie Cowboys if I got any beef. I'm gonna Jamie. I got you
Yeah, Jamie will take care of you
Jamie Jamie Jamie Cowboys is his lawyer to you. I'll give you that shot to Jamie Cowboys
Yeah, she is and it's like it's an important it's important to have
Someone loyal to you and it's like and and it's a probably
He's always been since I've been watching you Jamie never left you. Yeah, she has all right Jamie. I've been I've had
Yeah, so I'm just gonna give
People a little space in the holidays. I know it gets stressful the holidays. Maybe it's like they'll be
Give me space then they go give me space
Not you may I could give you space space. I'm not gonna give you space
I want to get closer. I want to get closer. What?
Yo, what you Jamie love you try to put it on me Jamie
I'm gonna put it on you Jamie. Let me put it on Jamie Jamie Mary. I'm about to put it on
You want to get married to Jamie and I what I'm going to get married to you. I'm going to get married to
Mormons and so we
Yeah
No, why she's a cowboy why she can't be a cowgirl and then I'll serve to see you when she's busy
What you're not what you're not gonna service me with nothing
No, you good. No, no, DJ Electra. DJ Electra. We can make a service right there. Yeah
But you want to you add that yet her animated your your love with
No animation what the fuck you say what the fuck I'm not J. Don't stop being weird with me. I smack you
I'm being weird. Okay. Well, you're in love with the cartoon. Okay, so I didn't say where with the cartoon
Okay, so you've seen you've seen the yeah, I see how she looked like
What the fuck is mouth like that white lady stuff what what's mouth hugs mouth hugs wouldn't like you know
Open my mouth real wide and give you a hug and be down below
I don't do the kissing that good the fuck
No, I say I give you a kiss
to the little salmon
Hello
What you like what you gonna kiss a little salmon? Oh my god. Stop being gay. It's like it's too early to be gay, man
Come on. There we are. Oh, there you are. Come on. So sorry
Yeah, well, I wake up like this. I wake up like this and it's too early
All right, you see it worse. Break down break down pop up break break your ass down
We team beta you're we team beta web be that
I don't know. He doesn't come here anymore. And Ben Bita called me F-A-G-G-O-T last night and then she like told me today
I'm blocked because I called her a bitch. I mean, it's like hello. I mean, it's like
You do takes be the all the time. So stop it. No, I just texted her yesterday for like months. I
Sight you think I don't know you take you you takes be the all the time
I'm talking about I can show you
I texted her yesterday and the time before that was months.
Psyche, I mean Psyche, when you and Bita get, when Bita's mad, when Bita don't want to talk
to you no more, you stay reaching out to her, come on, stop it.
Oh, please, she wants to talk to me, please, she wants to talk to me, she wants to talk
No, you always reach out to her, Psyche.
Yeah, but she always talks about me.
Like, you got to learn when, when Bita says you don't want to talk to you, stop reaching
out to her, my nigga.
I mean, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, please.
You don't fuck Gucci no more.
When a girl said, don't talk to me no more.
I need space.
Gotta give her a space.
That's for straight people.
That's like straight people.
No, no, no, no, gay people.
I don't know.
Maybe a gay radio don't pick that on.
You should know what to say, man.
Aren't you gay?
No, I ain't gay.
I ain't gay.
You're not?
Are you sure?
I'm very sure I like
Rikers where you like we the
Of the prison ward or I could read the feet feet. I mean, it's like if you go to Rikers
They will leave you just like that. Would you would you be the pop would you be the same decide?
They would have put you in the PC. You stand. Oh, they would not they would not
You'd be in the J-Cats. I would be in the
You know when you call me a jcat you disrespect me right well, so what I don't care. What are you gonna do about it? Wow?
So if I call you
You disrespect me all the time, but you know what's the jcat right?
It is again nuts
Uh-huh. It's like a nut like you. No, nigga. J.C.A. is like a PDF and shit like that
Custody, but yeah, okay. Well, we can call them
So it's like how I know more slang in the West Coast more than you. No, I do. I knew the correct
Take the mentally unstable people
What do you do what are you gonna do to me?
Yeah, what's a fart? Oh, oh, that's disgusting. Oh
My god, that is so disgusting
Take that nigga
Okay, well, I'm not attracted to you anymore and
Take that bitch stay away from me
Please
Yeah, he gotta say that what you about to do it on me. No, I'm sorry nigga take that
That's it. Oh, like I shit crazy nigga. You're disgusting. You're disgusting. You're disgusting being your your an animal
He's imagine the poor poor woman that you heard that shit
Fought it on that nigga fuck out of you gassy bitch. Yeah, you give me gas bitch. It's a called gas lighting
That's what it is. Yeah, you gave me gas bitch
Well, okay, I'm not attracted to you anymore.
I'm not attracted to you anymore.
That's your rumble.
That's your rumble in my stomach.
I ain't gonna hold you.
Yeah.
I already knew it was coming.
That was a cost-started. I had to cost-start it, you heard?
Yeah, they were discussing it.
That is, that's the worst I've ever seen.
You're discussing it.
Why are you laughing like a 10-year-old?
Santa, you literally have the brain of a 10-year-old.
Yeah
Happy birthday paid I don't pay yesterday was Paige's birthday. I did it. I did do a show
I think it's still up. It says happy birthday. Prairie page. I know you weren't around yesterday. Hey, hey, and I was her birthday was yesterday
Yeah, I know that's what I said, and I did a show yesterday saying happy birthday. Prairie page
And we had a little birthday celebration. Yeah, I was hoping you show up
But yeah, you're probably busy, but um, I'm gonna I go fart on your pillow. W
Yeah, you the pink eye. W
Well, that's just unsanitary
What? I'm going to fall down by the pillow.
You can just look at your diet.
W.
What are you eating, Santa?
that's disgusting. When you roll
up for the weed, get that fart.
Well, thank god, thank god you're
2000 miles away. Well, I'm going
to start. Let me eat the white
castle. Oh my god. Hey, look
what I have, Sam. Here's
what I have.
It's like you fart cigarette ass.
Oh, shut up.
Look what I have.
It's like, fart smell like cigarette.
I fart in your eyes, man, and see how you like it.
Here.
Look what I have.
This is a two gram.
What's that got, man?
This is two grams.
Yeah.
Please don't make it Vanna's bed smell.
White gummy bear
Hey, Marcy. How are you? This is a white gummy bear of ape and I have another one too. This one is the dragon fruit
That's what I kind of like you are. You're a dragon fruit, you know, what?
You know what you're trying to say
I'm a fruit cake. All right. Why are you trying to have more fruity nigga? No, because oh, yeah, because
I'm fruity
That's what gives you an idea of food.
That's what you have, that's what you have gas.
Hey, shout out to the idea of food last night.
Hey, Katrina.
Yeah, you ate Indian food?
Oh my god, how does it smell?
Well, they're not am I my first don't stink man. Oh, they don't we're sure that
Only narcissists say that
Only narcissists
Oh my god, you're disgusting like it probably smells like stale hot dogs or something like that still hot dogs and like and like you know
I came home late last night
What you do you're out partying at the clubs?
That's the holidays, man
You're at I want to do shit
You don't want to do you're shopping for your Christmas presents for your loved ones
To me I get bunny outside. Okay. How much am I getting this here? What the fuck?
you
Yeah
Your Christmas list Santa
I don't even got a list. No, you don't have a list. Am I on your naughty list?
What hey, yo, what what's up with you?
Well, you woke up with the
What? Yeah, I did. No, my nigga go away. Yo, what? Yo, my nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga. My nigga
No, I didn't use the cement that's
That's what you do you take you make a cement woman and that's that's what you make
Is that what you do?
You make a sculpture of shape like a beta and that's what you make love to
Don't get hated on beta
I didn't tell Bita to block your ass, don't worry.
You already blocked me, so it's too, your, she's way ahead.
Bro, leave her alone, nigga.
You leave me alone, how about you leave me alone?
How about that?
She's like the other one, what's the other girl you stalk?
What's the other girl you stalk?
I don't stalk anybody.
Emma?
Leave Emma alone, man.
I don't, I don't, I've not even doubted Emma.
Stop screaming at me, man, stop screaming at me.
I'm not screaming, do you think this is screaming?
I can tell you screaming, but this is not.
I just make the phone, please,
my normal conversational tone, actually.
Yeah.
I know you were in love with be the same man like the trust be the nose. No, I'll fuck with be the
There's not trust me to be the dude. Be the never get me dirty be the see me see my
Yeah, just wait
Wait for her to betray you
Let me tell you there's a lot of there's a lot of people I face time and see my face. Oh my god
You want a face on me when you got to pay me $200 I'll face
I'm not paying shit for it. I'm up there. I'm too exclusive.
It's like I give you the smile and all that. I don't want I
don't want I don't want to be smiled up by you. 200. No, not
at all. Are you going to pay me 200 or no? 209. I'm a I'm a
exclusive face.
But be the I know why trust be the piece. I've never had to worry about be the doctor doctor
She's in she's not in your bank account and that kind of stuff. So, you know, you know, be that never I've came
Duffer be the plenty of terms. Oh my god poor beta. I wish she had to see that
Oh my god, what the fuck how many times have you jerked off for beta?
What are you doing? Are you going to the bathroom?
Why are you why are you watching boom you're doing shout out to the banger
Stranger shot to the banger
See kitty kitty
Your cat would love it
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No
I showed my cat. I think I think be this short the cat before. Okay. Well, I got a cue cat
So do I
It's it's one of them short cats short-haired cats there and be the hat be the new the name
Obsidian abyssey abe abyssinian. Oh, what abyssinian. No, it's like a it's like a short hair
But feel like a like it's like fuzzy a short hair fuzz
Okay, little fuzzy cat be the new the name
Is it a sphinx is it a hairless cat? No, no, no
Okay, I like it's I never felt a cat hair like that
Yeah, I forgot be that had the name of it
I'll go to short hair cat or a tabby or something like that
It's just short hair, but look like her hard hair. I mean her pattern is like a like a army fatigue
But she's like chocolate his camouflage a camouflage cat. Mm-hmm
Well, cool. Do you wear fatigues out in public?
Kiddie little oh my gosh. He looks just get a sight. Don't worry about it
All right, I'm covered in a blanket with Rudy over here. She's she loves Rudy
The girl cat or is it gay male cat?
Boo boo boo boo good morning Marcy. How are you guys? Hey Marcy
Yeah, I joined LES and the LES was really kind actually
You know he I don't think he liked me at first when he met used to be on my show, but now he has his own show
I think he's
I don't know if you're a stranger
You're so respectful
Nigga you don't even you pull that boy said hey, I'm using real music
Oh shut up
Shut up you stupid
I don't know if you're a stranger
I'm out to beat a shot to my girl be
She's the kid he played a boom just a tapanga
He was giving me some really good feedback too. So but I guess, you know, there's a lot of different
I'm dropping the link right now. There's a lot of
Yeah, are you you're on his panel if you don't like me he does like me salmon has a crush on lovely lady
I joined everybody's panel. Oh
I could join clumsy panel. I can't I was even big tea panel. I'll go anywhere. Love you, lady
Okay, I do
Okay, yeah, I don't I don't know what the price. Yeah, I just don't I just I try to like like know as little as possible
Sometimes because it's like there's just so many like things going on that it's like I don't
Um, yeah, I mean, yeah, you see psych what like a psych allows LD fuck you bitching about me fact
You you allow everybody
You know anybody on your show
Mega he never come on my show. Hi summer
You narrow so much. Oh, hey summer superstar. Hey my superstar
Hey morning, y'all
So psyche the only reason let's is be a nice to use because we are not
Supporting him right now, and if you support him, I'm letting you know now. I will block him every time he comes around
Okay, well he is talking about he is talking about an 11 women
He is talking about he's hanging out with PDF files and all kinds of other shit
And Oliver he's being nice to you is because he is an agenda. That's it. I'm just letting you know if he's here
I'm going to wreck your shit
Yes, there's a ghost called me last night and was like, hey
He's like I'm getting paid to wait about the college to like get you on alias channel
I don't know how goes for like my
I went over there and this like and then but then it goes started being abusive. So I I left the panel
Actually, he's on some kind of pain medication or something like that it gets him crazy. So
Yeah, I love kind of quickly, but well, I'm not upset with girls
Yes, I'm telling you
You need to leave that alone right now. It's like me. You got an episode on your plate. You don't need this
I'm telling you. I'm not joking it when it comes to that
Yeah, you heard some, right? That's it.
You heard some?
Yeah, I'm not really saying I'm going to be there, but it is considered as a favor to
Ghost, and that Ghost kind of turned on me, so I left, and so, but it was, I mean, I
was just saying, there's a lot going on in our community, and right now, he has to learn
a lesson. So I'm just letting you know, I'm not playing. I love you to death, and I support
you, I got your back, but I'm not fucking around when it comes to this L.E.S. show.
Well, you do your mod and you do what you gotta do, you know, I did I blocked him
I'm letting you know that right now. I blocked the last light. Okay
I'm not gonna lie to you. I'm not gonna hide behind your back about it or anything
He's doing some really foul shit right now. I mean, he's done he's done a lot of women in our community and everything
Okay, I didn't know
I know you didn't that's why I got that. No, I know you didn't that's why I came up and talked to you
No, because just very was in saying
We have videos and proof and everything like you see he needs to get his shit together for a little bit
Okay
Yeah
Don't give a fuck about you like I said the only the only reason he was being I see history
It's cuz no one is coming to his channel right now because he needs to learn a fucking lesson
I didn't see anybody really in the chat. It's a race on Miguel and that was pretty much it
Yeah, yeah
I don't think it's going on, but yeah, because I didn't try to stay out of my own controversy and then like, you know
Left to be let alone for a little bit, you know, I'll probably just try to stay out
I'm gonna try to stay up other shows for the time being stuff like, you know
The best
Yeah, yeah, he did and he threatened to talk to my son last night
Yeah
Basically had to leave all my all the discords where I saw that going on and like, you know
Stay in my own discourse. Yeah, fuck that nigga. Yeah
That's a summer. We're cooking with summer, you hear?
Summer got the winter sizzling right now.
You heard that?
That's probably exactly what happened, man.
I don't know what pages we're talking about, but yeah, the L.E.S. shit.
You want to know anything? I'll let you know, and I'll send you a bucket of receipts.
Oh, this smells, you know. We're home.
Okay, this smells so good. We got two days.
Yeah, I got it. I'm gonna take you today, Amanda. I love to sell people to see those pictures
What are you shopping I'm saying that
You're chopping up the beans or so
I'm drinking a good coffee to you I'm drinking my coffee from McDonald's almost done
It's green so it turns like clear
There you go
I'm about to get on my PC. Give me one second. I'm on my phone
Oh very good. Well today I'm probably gonna try to get it. If I'm not too sick
I'm still a little bit sick, but I might try to buy a few gifts today
Now I don't have to whisper. Thank you for understanding. It's like, you know, I don't ever come to you and do shit like that. But like, this is a pretty serious situation with less. And it was something that took over our community all day history. And it affected a lot of people. And he's, he's just doing, you know, sometimes motherfuckers just really need to figure some shit out.
He needs to figure some shit out because the day you think it's cool to hang out with PDF files
The day you think it's cool to threaten unalive women the day you think oh and easy also has been
I saw him once you just to let you know
I don't think it would be too smart or have less or easy around you right now
I might be for 20s. I heard a little bit like
I don't care if you like christine or not what what's going on has nothing is not okay
Yeah, well, no, no, I mean was I heard other people talking about and actually it has nothing
It's with her it's it has nothing to do with her
She's actually one of the people calling us it out because what's happening is not okay. Like I said last night
Yesterday was insane
Easy to run on a lot of people
Docs people and all kinds of other crazy shit
And it was we all know he's already got a history of doing shit. So I think it's fucking weird
And then LES is hanging out with PDF files. He thinks it's cool and I got proof of it
We've already sent him paperwork showing him that these are PDF files. I have a
Recording where he Marcy even was trying to tell him like go. This is not it dude
This is not what you do the thing this ain't what we do and he was like no, they're my friends
They got my back. They you know all this other shit that we had a recording of him talking to them telling him
Tell it asking the PDF files to look at the people
So that means anybody he's arguing with you know, I mean anybody at time for a shit
So they need to figure some shit out, but right now it's a no-support band on easy and fucking less
Okay, I hear you. Yeah, I'll just you know
I'll just let them in there in the chat. They can probably you know mods will probably take care of it
Oh, yeah, they'll wipe them out as soon
Okay
Well, thanks for letting me know.
Sam, that's coming back up.
Yeah, cool.
You get caught in the crossfire with so much bullshit,
and this is this one thing you don't need to be.
You know what I mean? It ain't worth it.
I do. It does happen.
Damn, somebody you see.
God damn.
Merry Christmas. Damn.
Merry Christmas.
That's what I like to do.
Thank you.
that
I mean, I think we can all agree that you don't hang out with PDFs and then and then when people tell you and show you paperwork
You don't sit there and see but they're my friends. They have my back
Well, then good they can have your back motherfucker because you will be pushed out every fucker community. I have anything to do with
Fuck him and fuck easy. And that's why I spend
It's me
Hi, Manda. Hey y'all
What's up?
So summer I've got my elves working in that last phone number. I got on him
Has been used within the last two weeks. I'm pretty sure it's a burner
But
Well my boyfriend's handling that part of it. Okay good
Yeah, I'm not playing with them. I'm not this. It's getting out of hand
Ridiculous and I'm over it. So it's gonna stop
I'm a mother where another and you know, no, no, you did. I'm not gonna tolerate it
I've been dealing with this guy for probably five years now, and this is the last time he's gonna threaten me. So
Yep. Well, he's from where he's from where he's from you don't you didn't know where he's from?
Uh, I'll send you some stuff say about you got it. Yeah, I mean, oh yeah. Yeah, send me send me
Yeah, well, this needs to be a community effort because we
It's not there's many more crime heights Brooklyn. You heard you know, I'm not I'm not scared to throw my hood down
Crown Heights, yeah, that is come see me. Y'all want to see me. I'm a whole different problem
Close to me
All right, it's not to you summer. Yeah, ain't no wrong we go we go we go Paula
We're not playing us. I just when you think it's okay to sit here and a lot of women online
When you think it's cool to kick it with PDF files when you think it's cool all that
I'm gonna show you
You are and if I gotta make a special goddamn trip don't think the fuck I won't
Fuck anybody thought I was but when you play with me in mines, huh, you get a whole new ball game, baby
I that's what fuck with you summer bitch
You go hard, but when they just fuck with you, you go even harder and I like that you got a you stand on business
That's our respect you summer and you do I'd like to the real life off line anything. I'll play those games
And we have you know, we have a lot of people that try to support these motherfuckers and they're sitting here
I act like this and treat everybody I got time for this shit and this is go it
I promise you one way or another this just go it
And the day you ever think you could kick it with a PDF file in my presence. I'll bet you done made that shit the fuck up
I'll run you out everywhere. I fucking go cuz see people know I don't just run with shit
You know what I mean? Like one I got receipts and two you got me fucked up. We all got kids. Don't play with me
Yeah, hey man, hey man, don't don't make yourself. I mean it's time to take out the
Yeah, there's a lot of people that are
I'm participating, but I want to I want the snake's head. Oh
Yeah, and all of it's all of it every single bit of it. Like I said, it is what it is
I just I know psyche gets caught up in a lot of shit
sometimes of his own doing and sometimes not of his own doing but I don't want him to write in this
Because I'm saying right now me as as hot as I am
Anybody gets in my way. I'm gonna trample over you period
Well one direction and I don't I'm sorry, man. I don't play when it comes to PDFs
One direction or PDFs supporters. I'm so sorry my bad. I need that word out
If he's at one location that I think he still is he's 380 miles from me
Another direction he's
If he's there, he's about five hours from me 40 minutes
I don't do illegal things. I do it by the book
Yep
Now you get
You know as we all talk shit we all have a good time we all you know, whatever like with the best of them
But there's a certain things that
Should not be acceptable and PDFs and PDFs supporters. I should like this. Where should this been going on? Yeah, I'm not playing this a dude
At all like I'm I'm invested now. I'm said toes
See if you can move me. I said this on studies panel earlier
And I don't know if you went back and heard this
He said he has been going to that area since before he was on TPP
He's lying dude. That's all he does is lie. That's like he's telling everybody
I don't know if you've heard the latest but now because I've been on that ass, right and he says he's feeling it
He's filling the people on seven. He's feeling them. I fuck is not going to chat all that. He's filling it, right?
So now he says he's in danger
He says the only reason he's friends with them is because he they're gonna hurt him and his family
Well, I can think season a fucking movie
movie time, right? We're about to show that action. We're about to perform. We're about
to perform for this movie. Let's get that. He's scared. We got childs, actresses, actresses.
Let's go.
I get it's the internet and everything but like you got me fucked up man like leave me to fuck alone leave minds alone and
Don't play in front of my face because if you do
Down kitty and don't think I'm not out reach summer and but I have to stay focused
I have to whatever said
That's a thing though. I could be in that position to talk shit because somebody gonna stay on that ass by everything else is
Going down too. So you know what I mean? We all got a position to play
That's a fuck I've been working on it all night
My boyfriend woke me up at midnight and he said what's the deal with the guy?
Toting he said I got you
So I got to call him back in a few minutes. He's not home. He's out of town. He'll be back this afternoon though. Oh
Yeah, like I said all these old three situations there that will PDF group
All of them all three of them easy less and his little fucking PDF friends. I'm not playing around and everybody's gonna fill it
They want to keep fucking playing that shit yesterday was I'm not no
There has to be some kind of fucking tolerance that and us as women on in the first place have to deal with a lot of bullshit
Like a lot of bullshit, but you think you're gonna get comfortable and tell all fuckers you love them. Okay play
Let's play let's play motherfucker
Well, and for him to also say, this is what really got me again, when he said, I'm going
to take your information and put it on the dark web, tells me that you know how to get
there and you've been there and you probably spent a lot of time there.
Okay, well, yeah, that's what these sick motherfuckers exactly exactly and so I would let us sit in here
And he's all like they're my friends
They got my back and then on the phone when I'm talking about some oh, yeah
I got two Facebook's come hit me up because I got some people. I want you to look into
What?
I promise you I'm gonna send you all the same man. I never got
So easy is threatening to unalive people because there's a couple things go out of
I'm threatened to unalive people and specifically women so he's got a total woman
He was gonna unalive himself
Unalive her and unalive himself and not in his bitch. Okay, it's Christine actually
He told that to Christine and he said a whole bunch of the crazy other shit
And then
Les is talking about mad shit lying on this fucking dick talking about these fucking people that he ain't ever fucked
Being a fucking weirdo and hanging out with PDF files and saying they're all his fucking friends and all this other
Also, they your friends. Okay. Well, cuz that's regular people. We don't do that. So that's there's just your friend cool
You go on over. It's like I move I got another community and whoo-hoo. Okay, cool
Cuz my focus is mass on something cuz you know, we don't fuck with PDFs or PDF supporters
So especially my crew like negative. I don't know the fuck you thought this was I
Wish like you
And that is one of them
Yeah, sure you say you don't say to the female like I go I go I like the drama
This limits to this shit man
Bitches whores all that I'm down for all that I don't care about that
But when you over here tell myself I'm a lot of my I'm a lot of you and a lot of myself or
You over here making excuses and kicking them with fucking PDF files
Yeah, I ain't got time for that because see what he's doing what less is doing and he don't even realize it
Is he's hanging out with these motherfuckers? Of course, we don't like PDFs
So we call that shit out which puts all of us in danger which Amanda already has a fucking history with this motherfucker
threatened our life. You know what I'm saying? You see the
follow-ups of all this? Yeah, and they go bring more than
where those right and you bring in the morning's weirdos into
our like in our situation. The fuck is wrong with you? I'll
give you that. I 100% agree with that. Yeah, all because I
told less me and exiled both told less that you know what
that dude's about and I can't
I can't in good conscience not warn people. I cannot because there's a lot of things that I play about and I know it's YouTube and we're here for entertainment.
But that's where I draw a line in the sand and I'm not making police reports. I'm not calling my local PD. I call agencies. Okay.
And if it comes to that, that's exactly what I'll do.
And I'll tell him exactly where he's fucking out. I'll go on record. So he says he's gonna sue me
I said, please do so that way I can have you cross examin on the witness stand on the record
Please
And he goes to now subpoenas and said i'm like, baby. Okay, cool. I'm a court. I just want to do court advocacy
Okay, like I mean i'm just saying that's like real life is what I do
So you want to play in my playground? Let's go
Just tell them niggas pop out in Brooklyn. We have a nice talk with them.
They're too busy trying to think they're going to attempt to play with women.
But I'm going to tell you right now, I'm not a woman you're going to play with,
because I'll go toe-to-toe. I don't give a fuck.
I've been dying to me somebody up. I've been dying to me somebody, man.
You know what I mean? Like I said, we could talk shit, bitches could be horrors.
We could do all of that. I don't care about that.
But when you start making real life fucking threats,
I got you bitch, especially when you got a history of already doing the type of shit
Goof. Yeah. So it hits different when you already done stupid shit online. Goof. I can show you Yu-Gi-Oh
Goof, I'll show you some Yu-Gi-Oh. You pop out with your faggots as bait clips. Yeah, y'all weird
You goof and bait clips is weirdos, but go ahead. You can pop out and come too
You could bring K twos without K. I do a K hated site not K
K is a modern site. It's crazy. Yo, what y'all need to be flip-flopping too much my first summer
I'm gonna send you another email because I don't want to put this out in the atmosphere
I have somebody very close to this individual that ham is
But yeah, it's just I don't know. They're like I said the shit that just has been going down and and you know
The crazy thing about a Sam and it is Marcy, you know Marcy
So she sits for a good 20 to 30 minutes try to tell us a less this isn't it like
Like supporting and giving a space to PDF files like this ain't what we do, baby
Like you can't do this. You know what I mean? Like you can't do this and she's talking to him and telling him and every single time
He's coming back with why why he wants to hang out with them why they have his back
Why he's friends with them they see the things that we all say to him. They'd be watching everybody
They don't come in in but they'd be watching every single. You know, I mean just make it like okay cool
So do you make it a very hard line that these are your friends?
So we're gonna do Sesame Street and you go on over there my fucker because you ain't wanted over here
He wanted me to come on panel earlier and you notice I didn't because I was very angry and I have to stay focused
But I let him know clearly to his face. I don't appreciate being lied to I don't appreciate
Any of it. I'm disappointed and I'm disgusted and to come back and try to spin the narrative and say that
You know if somebody was after me, I would very say that go ahead. Yeah, if somebody was after my family
I'd fight back. I'm not gonna take it lying down. I'm not gonna go kiss some motherfuckers ass
Summer yeah, I know I dealt with terrorists of that that are
Exactly then fucking
Sumber, okay, I'm just gonna do the fact that now listen this so that let this is the yo when this shit when he said this shit last night
When he went live last night, I was like, oh my lord. I made some good homemade potato potato soup, but shit was fire
She was really good. Anyway
when he sat there and he was like you really want to know you want to know
why I'm hanging out with you want to know why because they got stuff on me
they got stuff on me they they go they gonna go after my family because
everything's above of it
above of it, above of it, that's how he says irrelevant.
That's how less says irrelevant.
Above of it, it's a fucking class.
But anyway, like my thing is,
and then in the same breath of air,
he's like, remember that one time
you came up on your son's laptop summer?
Keep playing with me.
Bitch, my son laughed, my son was standing right here,
my son laughed, my son's grown.
He was like, he's a clown.
He said, you think I'm worried most of mine own my name?
I
Just want to say shot to low east side. I'm connected to Louisa. Y'all niggas is keep talking about LES
All this low east side nigga shot to my shot to Smith shot to shot to
I'm not even gonna say a lot
Low east side shot to canal nigga niggas push that man out there. They know me and hit different
Who's this guy turd? I heard turds, uh, is this guy turns the other one or no?
No turds cool turds the one turd
There was a big misunderstanding between you have a black rg on the panel
Which i'm not gonna put anything into that because right now to me and I love stay turds to death and I love you know
I like rg, but it's not important so the bigger picture right now
Is it?
You feel me
Like the bigger picture is that less is hanging out and supporting PDF files.
The PDF files are now coming into our community, trying to harass people and less
think he's cute and got something up his little ass and then easy being stupid as fuck too.
So that's to me the bigger picture right now.
Okay, saying your brother or your baby daddy's that went to jail, okay?
To turtle.
Say your, say your baby daddy's that went to jail or your brother that supports you, you fucking
Don't fuck you think you you cuz you talking shit about big T
I'm not allowed to talk about you you you docks family members. Okay, you docks my family
Don't never forget that bitch. You and Barry your fucking scumbags
Here come Barry complaining about child support niggas mention a child support here
But yeah, you're docks and family members shut the fuck up and sit the fuck down
All I say you talking about psych now you suck a psych dick of being a mod same thing you did with KK
Just shut the fuck up and sit down you gross fuck you're ugly disgusting bitch
That's why Barry don't want to fuck you. I never seen a bitch pay a nigga so much money and the niggas didn't even hit
The niggas didn't hit
The reason why I'm bringing this up because I want people to know like these these PDFs are starting to try to come in people's communities
You know what I mean? And so on my page
I'm gonna be showing pictures and names and shit like that because I and these are certified they have paperwork
Okay, so like we all do our shit. We all talk our shit
We all do you know do our drama and all the crazy shit that we fucking do
But you know I'm saying I don't think any of us stay one any of them kind of motherfuckers
So because of love that being friends with them now they think they're gonna try to start entering people. That's how it works
And they're already doing it. So I'm letting y'all know because you know I'm saying like me me know a psych brought
You know psych popping up on my panel one day brought a whole community two communities to blend together
But I don't fuck all that dude. I ain't blending with no PDFs. Oh, so so whoa, hold on
So you don't come so you insight community never was together. Yeah, but now so I came to my channel one night
We part of the
Nah, me and Scythe came friends. Scythe popped up on my talk your is channel one night
We was all doing a late-night panel Scythe popped up and I was like, oh wait a minute
I like you so he kept coming around a couple times and then I was like yo
I was like give me a link. I want to share it out and our two communities merged together
Okay
Now some people in the community knew about each other, but a lot of people did
Like I like to I like sometimes. Oh, well, I'll be in a bad person
I know I join your panel sometimes, but I definitely I'll be I'll be joined. I'll be I enjoy your panel space
You got a lot of different people. I don't see a lot
Because I belong to a lot of different communities and one thing that I love that is to merge communities together
So I feel like it's my responsibility of some majors going on to be like, yo
Everybody needs to be aware of this shit because we're not supporting that shit
They need to get this shit together. I like that. I'm Mexican. God. He's funny
Have you said God? He's very I like and I don't see him nowhere else, but your panel
You know, you know how yeah, I love the content you shout it to the content
Talk about what I've heard and what you caught but StayTart is the one that brought the video of him actually talking to the PDFs
So like I've known StayTart for a long time and I mean he's cool dude. He's good people's like
There's some other shit going on, but for like I said to me
It's not important, but it's for me in this bigger conversation. This is what's important right now
I'm just not gonna get caught up in that because it happened yesterday and I just came what's important is people need to understand that
If you start seeing certain people in your shit,
block them, motherfuckers.
And last, you on pause right now.
You need to get your shit together.
Yeah, there was a little tiff last night.
I have somebody doing a little recon for me.
There's been a little fallout between Sausage Dave and Thumper,
but they'll be back together tomorrow.
Yeah, this doesn't look like it's so weird.
And the fact that the paperwork is since the last and less was like,
let's tell Marzy, I've seen the paperwork.
I mean, you know, he said that the pictures ain't him.
Like, he, he's...
Let's fix this glue or something.
And that's why I said like you already told him the history and the threats he had made to you and how serious the shit was
You know, I mean how serious it got right? Oh, and he didn't take and the fact that he turns around and be like
Okay, cuz like I'm gonna tell you right now if I come across and this is a real life because I do that
I do the call it out like
Taking and putting PDFs in jail. Okay, that's what I'm a part of in real fucking life and anybody can look me up and see that
So you get them right online. I'm not playing that shit dude. I'm just not and he's gonna sit here
And if so if we see anybody we'll we'll get to where we can get the paperwork on them because fuck some rumors dude
I've rumors or bullshit
I mean because and on YouTube anybody puts jackets on anybody
But when you got fucking paperwork and you give it to somebody and they make fucking excuses
Tell me something. Oh, that ain't really the paperwork. It ain't real
the fuck
Yeah, he even when you and he says you hang out with PDF files because you take PDF files down
As an alias to try to keep yourself hidden that tells me all I need to know
Dude, he's it's just the logical thinking. It's just not fucking there
It's not and something like I said, man, I'll talk shit with the best of them
I would talk shit with the best of them
But goddamn there's gotta be a certain failure and I'm just not playing this shit
So the reason why I came up here is because last night last came into this chat
I blocked his ass and then I came up with a psyche because I'm not gonna I'm not gonna let him
Be blindsided on what's going on either because he deserves
I mean people put psyche is so much shit or he gets himself in so much
It or whatever the reason is this ain't got nothing to do with him and he don't need to catch no strays
But I'm telling you I'm yeah, I'm gonna chase him out everywhere. I go until he gets to sit together
You want to hang out with PDS? Cool, go hang out with them motherfuckers.
That's just where I'm at right now.
Good morning, motherfuckers.
Sorry, Mrs. Wilson.
You ain't got to like me to hear what the fuck I'm saying, by the way.
Sorry, you were too much.
Yeah, you need to get a Z-pack or something, babe.
I know, it's been a few days.
I'm just smoking a weed. There's a there's supposed to be some kind of like flu type style thing or whatever that
Everybody's gonna hold you back
Oh hell no, they're psyched oh fuck you're too low Z pack you'll be good to go
How does it- Christmas is in a few days. I guess it's what is it 20th today? Okay, so five days.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I forgot. And Katrina put it-
Yeah, Les, Les has got this whole new thing because he's lying on his dick, talking about he's fucked this broad and never even fucked her.
Never fucked her at all.
And sit there swerves up and down he fucked her then I'll say he didn't fuck her
Then he said he's so stupid dude, then he fucking sit there and said well, it's a reverberant
That's where the whole irrelevant thing comes from
Because I fucked her back in the day motherfucker the time and you gave she would have been 11 years old
You're like 10 years older than her so you would have been grown the fuck
His real age either he wouldn't give Lisa his real age
No matter what he gives he everybody knows who he is now. I mean, that's that's already said girl. You talking about less
He wouldn't tell her his real age he you know trying to I mean, you know the deal
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, see now
I didn't because I was listening to something else and I got to go back somebody sent me the clip though of Lisa
I know she was I know she was frustrated. So I sent her a text last night when I finally get offline
to just check on her but then I realized it was like almost 11 I was like oh man that one's sleeping
I'm a fucking jackass yeah you were making potato soup then and
when she was up on his panel yeah I had peaked in a couple of times and that's when I heard him say
you know that one time you came up on your son's laptop my son was standing right here he was like
He goes, he says, you one time you came up on your son's laptop, keep playing with me like he's gonna dox my son
My son was like, okay
Like, I don't know dude people are weird
That's her go-to when you find out that you've been hanging out with PDF files and people's not told you once and not told you twice
And they didn't make excuses for it like
And then the other one you not gonna say her so much you got a lot of yourself and a lot of a woman like now
We're not doing that
Yeah, that's wild. That's a wild shame it
Like we're not doing that
Over over your name and shit getting Docs, but mind you my fucking done Docs everybody in a mama
So you done Docs all kinds of people, but then you upset cuz you get Docs what and your responses to tell my fuckers
I'm on myself and a woman
And anybody that is attached to it pretty much. Oh, okay
Wait
So anybody ready for Christmas
Yeah, shout to Christmas shout to the holidays happy holidays
This afternoon
Everyone has a name to this Mosul
At some point today, I got a sometimes this week. It's sometimes before Tuesday. I have to make up shit. Oh the Christmas bags
It's gonna be fun
Feliz Navidad
Happy holidays, Merry Christmas. Happy
Kwanzaa, you know shot to my Jewish people. Yeah
So I get nothing for Christmas. She's Jewish
Yeah, but don't they get don't choose people like get a bunch of gifts. No, they don't do nothing out. They do the
Yeah, they do they do I think every time the light or mora right side
And they spend it in the cradle, but they get like really like they get instead of getting like one big gift
They get like a lot of little gifts, but it's yeah, I got like chocolate coins
Hey
Like I don't have little kids anymore my kids are girls, so I buy baby dolls
Has anybody bought a baby doll and it's been more expensive because I remember Trump would say like well
You ain't got about four baby dolls. You can just buy one baby doll for Christmas
I was just curious if the baby dolls are more expensive do we need to save the baby dolls like
I mean they do a lot of stuff
I see that more jet they burp or more mechanical now
Oh, yeah, I mean said there's dolls out there that
People make that move like real babies and said I'll be like damn, okay
So yeah, all the toys so it'd be cool to I wish sometimes I wish all my kids were a little now because all the toys
Thing about being a parent you get to
You don't say just have fun
God bless. That's what you Katrina. I think it's more expensive. Yeah
And it lasts longer back in the day. He's the last toys. He's the last one. Yeah, they're throwing together now
Just like cars houses everything's just instant. We live in an instant society
Let's say you know it is what it is
We have those babies though
You put the bottle in its mouth and the liquid would kind of disappear and then you
Never understood what a damn liquid went I know I'd be trying I was like
So I hear sleep streams are like a thing I know psyche's done a couple but I was talking
to some other people and they were like yeah I do what I do so I'll be getting big numbers
so then let the night I was just kind of going through lives or whatever you know how they
didn't go through the stroll or whatever and there was tons of people sleeping on stream
and there was tons of people in their fucking chat and I was just what is what is it about
Don't know a lot of people do it
And they make big numbers. I mean like that. I'm not hating it all cuz I fall asleep on panel all the time
So I'm not saying that I'm the Dory is if I'm on panel late at night. I'm probably gonna fall asleep like this
But yeah, I don't get it
in the chats can be fun sometimes and
So
They I don't know. I don't think ours was called baby alive in 1980. I don't think it was called baby alive
Baby alive. I remember that thing
Yeah, the name sounds familiar, but this was a tiny bottle that you would buy and when you tip the
There was a white there was a milk. There was the orange juice. Yeah
Yeah
You tip it and it would just magically disappear a whole bottle full of the only thing I came that came to a conclusion of filing when I was grown is what I think they did is instead of filling the whole bottle up they just outlined the bottle and so it looked like the bottle was being filled up and then just everything was going up and selling up well that's the only thing that makes sense to me.
Still have all my cabbage patch dolls in storage
Cabbage those are ugly. Oh, I loved them
Who did so I said someone looking at cabbage patch. Oh, yeah, um, you know Jim next boyfriend
Yeah, we didn't feed it actual milk or anything my baby doll didn't do any of that
You know
Base surfer base surfer looks like a cabbage pet still to me. Oh
Wow
Morning, good morning, it's sunny. Yeah, good supposed to be warm today. It's been so fucking cold
Yeah, I'm fixing to jump down guys, it's almost 8 a.m. Here. I'm trying to stay awake
A nice day
Thanks for letting me up. Yeah, I'll probably be in the chat
Yeah, I think I'm gonna jump down to you
All right, thank you get some medicines when you feel better try not to let stuff bother you
You got a lot of people that care about you and support you. Thank you. I love you
You know, I'm not around all the time, but one or times a busy time of the year for me. So, um,
You know, I'm always doing shit, but I'm around so you got people to support you
Holler
Shut your summer man
Should I go eat that eat that rat again? Would you eat a rat on our far much?
Yeah, you would piece of the rat eat your rat
Piece of the rat or the one a cat eat it put it in your mouth and then shake it up
Shake it up shake it up a little
I don't got none they can shake it up a little for it. Yeah
I'm going to have to do it.
You queen free lion in the house.
You're going to do it all night long standing, right?
No, I'm not doing nothing to you.
You go grab that fucking rat on the cat, and then you go, yeah.
Give me a dream. Give me. I'll go give you a nightmare. You know what your nightmare is. You know what your nightmare is going to be.
I don't know what your nightmare is right now. Having to talk to you on a panel.
You know what your nightmare is. You know what's going to be the nightmare?
What's going to be the nightmare? You know what's going to be the nightmare?
What? What is it?
Cleaning that fucking carpet. That's going to be your nightmare.
I have a vacuum cleaner right here.
Yeah, it's clean it up.
We'll let's let's do the content.
Let's see the inside of your toilet.
I want to see the inside of your toilet.
Show me how that looks.
Can you show that?
Oh, it looks very clean.
Oh, it's very clean.
Oh, OK.
What you want to bet?
I bet you.
All right.
Show a little box.
I showed my inside.
So I bet you my inside told us way cleaner than your little box.
I guarantee that.
Let's make this content right now.
I already showed my little box.
No, no, no.
Show right now.
Don't touch it.
And we do it for the.
You're first. You first. No, I was due at the same time. I don't mind. I don't mind doing that for the content. You're gonna, you're gonna rip me off. No, why would I rip you off? You know, I'm not mad at my word. No, you're not. Wow. So come on. That's the content. No, no, no content. Wow. That's one, two, three and came up. I just got to go back on my phone.
I didn't know what you looked like. Oh, well, if I do know you look like you look like a cross-eyed fool, but that's all
Well, I see I seen a video of you was selling a huge deal
Right
selling you go there
Weren't you?
Then you said selling you go stop playing with me. No, I'm on you. Yo, it was not the you go south to the you go
Okay, it was you. Yeah. Okay. I was right
Okay, it's okay if you play you. Yeah. Hey, I played magic the gathering until I was like, you know, 13 years old
So I should have tapped that land. You heard you know, you know how to tap lands. I
Know how to tap that ass. What the fuck? Why are you being gay man?
Magic is still good. Magic is still good magic. Don't make money. Okay. Hey, hey, they're coming for you, Samman
Wow. Wow. He's I'm black. Yeah, exactly. You're a black or Puerto Rican
I'm Puerto Rican Dominican, okay, that black is that black or you're African you tell me what was Dominican people?
They're like Mexican or Spanish or Spanish
You tell me spanish
It's like a they have like you know they speak Espanyol
Do they speak I don't know no you tell me Puerto Rican is more like Spanish than it is I'm Puerto Rican and Dominican
Yes
Before we can Dominican. Yeah, you're so you'd be considered Hispanic. I think you tell me
Who I'm calling you look pick up pick up look open your door
I said you a delivery pick up your I got to deliver your front door ASAP open the door your
Hold it down
What kind of stuff you like? Huh site open the door man. I got a special delivery for you
You like heavy stuff and it's not that it's not the hook. No daddy
Go open the doors. Like I that was the call. I was ready for that call
Get that you don't have to mute papa. Let's hear that call
Ring ring ring ring ring phone call phone call delivery delivery
You too Jimmy Cowboys. Oh
You put Cowboys because you're a Cowboys fan
Shout out to you. I am a Cowboys fan too. I'm from New York though Cowboys ruin my my my career
With football so I took Tony Romo. That was my quarterback. That was my quarterback
That was my quarterback. We had a chance with Tony Romo. Then we had we had to oh
Then we had that's Brian shout to that fucking bullshit catch that they took back that's briar
Yeah, and then this guy that that's Prescott. He ain't it. He ain't it. He ain't it
That's Prescott. He ain't it
Jamie Cowboys. No dishes, but he ain't it
He ain't it man. He ain't it already for so long
Oh
Yeah, there is a circular saw it was on yesterday. It's like people across the street doing it
But if anyone needs some uh, you know, you know, why you so skinny man. I'm so skinny because you know, what happened?
Hey, what happened to you? What happened to you, bro?
I've always been skinny. Oh my god. No, you never was this skinny. What the fuck is that?
See that that's from like the mouse pad. You know put the lotion and put a lotion on it put a lotion
What?
You wrote some lotion on it please. Okay. Yo site. Nah, you wasn't this skinny, bro. You wasn't this skinny. Yo, somebody get well
No, what's what's the last time you a site?
How much do I weigh like one?
No, what's the last time you ate? What's the last time you ate?
I like yesterday a McDonald's and I'm gonna. Well, what you have what you what you have for McDonald's. I mean
I mean, I look I'm gonna eat right back in front of you. What what what?
McGrittle and you know
coffee, a little.
No, no lotion. I need some lotion right there. Look how dark. Look how bad it looks. My nigga. That looks like a bedbug bite
What though? No, that's a bad bug bite. That's a bad bug bite. That's a bad bug. That's a bad bug. I know what I see it
Hey, hey, the cat hungry the cat hungry look he's gonna have some bacon in a little bit. You're gonna have some bacon
Yeah, that's a I like that one that what what's what what my name is that cat?
That's mr. Tricks
Tricks I like tricks tricks is that's a big cat right there. Look at that boy
Yeah, he's a little boy. He's a little cute little boy.
Oh, and you like to be pet on the head?
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, you're like when you rub your head, oh, you love it.
Where's the one with Lucille?
What's her name, Lucille?
I think it was.
I said Lucille.
Who?
Yo, how about her?
Lucille.
I used to have a bird game, Lucie.
Like, that was for Lucille.
Shout to Lucille.
I know, but it's OK as an occasional treat.
Low battery, it's OK to have a little bit
as an occasional treat.
Wow, see, Arthur.
Arthur, see, when you come on my panel,
I don't want to hear nothing.
Arthur, so you be dick-sucking after old said man. I miss you man. Yo, man Arthur Arthur Arthur
Yeah, shut the fuck up. Look Arthur wants you want to suck your cock. Look Arthur want to suck your cock. Yeah, oh
After he's the best cop sucker. Yeah, Arthur is the best
Fucking cock sucker bitch
Okay, uh, no, all my
tricks tricks isn't that all the cats are but tricks is like a homebody like usually the reason I would get a fix is because they wander
The trick doesn't wander. He's like a little like homeboy. Here go some catnip
Let the catnip. Oh, no, no, he about to get them excited. Little he about to get them excited. Oh
Like that here
Oh, I
Thought he's gonna put it on your chest. I thought what kind of weirdo shit you about to be on oh my god
Oh my god, he's about to have a freak off.
He's about to have a freak off.
Oh no, he's about to have a freak off with the cat.
Oh, I don't know, this is crazy.
He put it all over his chest, yeah.
His thing is, wow, his thing.
Pack him up, y'all.
He's not gonna spray, he doesn't spray.
He doesn't really spray.
You gotta wash your eyes you kind of probably smell you're fucking up the catnip
That is a big cat
all over your body
That's a big cat
He is
He's a very good cat. He's actually of Lola's like Lola. I have Lola to Lenore and Lola and he's um, he's Lola's son
No, no, I was fixed but you're the kid and the little is fixed now. Oh my god. Oh
You smell it. Oh my god. Oh, oh, he pooping. What is that? Not his balls. Oh
Hey yo, hey yo, hey yo, hey yo, hey yo, that's the first time I've seen cat balls.
I gotta stop smoking. I gotta stop smoking. I gotta stop smoking. Yeah, I'm a goofy nigga
I'm a goofy nigga guys down. I'm like, what the fuck is that? I'm like, he pooped. He put the poop
Oh happy holidays. Yeah, I
Apologize, it's the first time I ever see about fall
That's a Topanga
Well, what it is can you can you go take the camera? Oh
Look at this one too
What is it come on show me Papa show me let the content content you see
Open it up open it up. No, it's a dead mouse in it. It's in a bag open it up. Listen, open it up
I'd rather have dead mice than alive ones. Oh
Open it up I dare you come on
There's a dead rat inside of it. They will eat it. They will eat it. They eat live rats
No, I'm
Put it put it put it in the McDonnell bag
It came with the McDonald's
Who
Look the cat hungry look look
Donald's here
This cat loves cream watch this
Damn yo, he sure is a liquor. God damn me. He licking that up. Damn. He eating that up. Oh, he munching it
Not good. Oh
We finished off the whole thing. Okay, one another one
Oh, there he is. There's Rudy. Hey, you know, am I the best thing? Are these the best right here?
Potato.
Why you? Why you like me? Yo, that shit is crazy.
Isn't that gross this one sent me that dead rat?
I thought it was like a catnip. That's somebody like a neighbor left me catnip or something for Christmas like a nice little gift.
It's a dead rat. I mean the cats, I'm not gonna let the cats eat it cuz I don't know
been sitting in my door, my door all day.
Then why are you eating your potato like that like you never ate look at you like what?
No, you okay, man, you okay
Yo, this shit is crazy. They said it you okay, papa delicious
You didn't wash your hands
Look, you didn't wash your hands
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yes, it is
Yeah, Rudy is skinny man. Rudy knows not Rudy is skinny. Nah, fuck out of you. I'm not even gonna talk about that Rudy need to eat
He's drinking cream. No Rudy need Rudy need more than cream
Rudy need like the booty reals. You can see rescue site rescue Rudy hashtag
Look at Rudy Rudy don't even look the same. Oh, no, that's not the that's not the one
What's the one with this? Well, I can see his ribs. That's that's that's the person you're that's when you're talking about is Rudy
He's fine. No, that's not the one
Pick them up
No, the mouse was not sent with my delivery food that was separate. Thank God, but it's probably been there all day
I haven't been out of the house yesterday
Well, but I want to thank the person that sent me the food. Thank you so much. This is delicious
No, I think yeah, I think you switch your cats man. I'm not switching cats. That's him. Where'd he go Rudy?
He's over there. How many cats you got now? How many cats you got now at four for for months and months and months?
Well, well one named um, I think you only got three now. Damn. You only got three now at four. I've Lenore Lola
Tricks and Rudy. Yeah, it went from nine to four shit crazy
Because I had two litters. I actually had three. Crazy.
Four, nine to four. Pay attention from nine to four.
Nine to four. Pay attention to your homework.
Hey, look at this.
Look, look, look, look, look. He get excited. Look, cookies.
Look, you about to stash that so you could, that's for dinner.
Look, look, he don't want to eat that. Look, that's for dinner.
Look, what the, this thing ordered bacon just like that from McDonald's?
was a gift that's that's that's Liz that uh that's him all right L3 let me see that we got we got
to get a Rudy check and we got to see this Rudy that's the root cat you saw him Rudy
got to pick him up we got to see what's going on with Rudy big it's not good for cats man
oh you like that bacon huh he's like it's better than right yeah magic much with neighbors house
Oh, there you go. Is that yummy? Here. Go eat it. Here.
There's Rudy over here. He's fine. He's absolutely fine. Let me
see. Let me see. There he is right there. Hey Rudy. Come
come. We gotta come in. Well, he's scared of you. Lil'
up. Not scared of me. No. Oh, I see it now. Oh, yeah, I see
it. Yeah, that's her. Well, you don't see Rudy. What you
what's the cat food? Are you a cat food? You know, you know
how old Rudy is?
Yeah, that'll mean nothing. Oh, do you think yes? Well, you know, you know, you don't think they lose weight as they get very very old
No, I see an older cats fat. I
Seen a lot of I did my homemaker cat. You know, I'm babysitting. I'm babysitting the cat for a while now
I do my homemaker cats. He's not a fat cat. He's fine
He looks old. Yeah, he's 17 or 18 years old. I don't mean nothing. He eats. Okay. This person's getting banned from the chat
It's just what happened. Why are you getting mad? What? Oh my god. Why are you getting mad? Let the check egg low key kitty gang
Wait, what he kicked himself like now he got mad look you know you want to eat the bacon all by himself
Look now, but we told him to share. We told
Rudy come here
See he's eating some he's having some bacon. Yeah, just give him real food
Some blue mountain
So I
Didn't go to the computer. I just accidentally clicked myself off. Hey, man
Here you go
Actually, I clicked myself off. This is really good. Yeah
I'll go yell a blogger for you, he may at all.
You can throw a blogger in his life.
Oh my gosh, this is the thing.
My favorite is a McGrittle,
sausage egg and cheese McGrittle.
You know, if you get the egg McMuffin,
that's like the real egg,
you know, and McDonald's is the best egg
they can get you at McDonald's on the egg McMuffin,
but this is good egg too, I like it.
Look, look, look, he's like, he just came home, like look.
You look like a madman you got rabies
You got rabies man
So no more date where you were Alex on your birthday
What you feel about that
Mm-hmm. He has no right to stay here
Hmm
What's your thing about that? Oh, it's original Yu-Gi-Oh Yu-Gi-Oh master
Yu-Gi-Oh Yu-Gi-Oh Yu-Gi-Oh. Yes, Yu-Gi-Oh
Alexander if she released it of the DMs, that's fine, but I just want to tell
I was not we should release release the DMs first release the DMs first
I got you at the first these are DMs. Yo send me the DMs. I got you release them. She read them already
Word. Yeah
So give me the DMs
She read them so I can read them
Well, no, no, no, no, no, send it to me. I'm gonna see that I won't see the deals for myself
You'd be lying to me
I'll be over it anyway. It's too depressing right now. Wow. Wow. Just you can read them. You'll read them read it
I'm just gonna her chat. You go to her channel. She did a half hour special about me yesterday, so
You can hear her side of the story that you can question me on it
But it's a misunderstanding that's what the title of the stream is misunderstanding
Okay, you know what? I'm okay. You know what? I'm laughing you gave a man more than a kid. He's doing fuck you
Okay, I'm laughing at that
Okay, go cover big T take go cover big T K cover big T big T has so many words for you. Don't fucking bitch
Why are you paying?
Why are you paying big T's niece name? How about that fucking disgusting bitch?
Okay, hello, okay, go pay for dick
Imagine paying for dick you still don't get it
You talk mad shit you talk mad shit about psych now you suck in his dick get the fuck out of here
You can talk mad shit about psych and now you are my first site just like you did with elbow
Just like you did with KK just like you do where everybody else the same thing you did with Zaya
You chose mad shit about Zaya peps and that girl you went over there and went back to donate shut the fuck up
Nobody give a fuck about you bitch. You're a fucking loser. Don't suck a dick bitch. We need to suck a dick
The best seven years you ugly
hawk
I don't know what what what do you even look like?
Yes, I guess a bitch ass nigga, I don't kiss like ass
I don't I don't I don't have to kiss a psych ass to be on his panel like y'all
Go away
Magic kiss
Imagine
Yeah, you have to kiss my ass a little bit. I mean at least be nice thing on my own show
You don't have to call me a B a n on my own show. Have a very nice
But thank you for being on the show
But you have something else to say what what nigga, I'm not kissing your ass to be on your panel my nigga
Well, then bye. No, no, I'm not I'm not you have to be respectful because you're on my show
On your show imagine. I'm not Kate. I'm not these people gotta kiss your ass to be on your panel
I mean, jeez, at least not disrespect me blatantly.
Here you go, baby.
My kid.
Oh, there you go, baby.
What?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
What? What? I can't. What? I
can't. You're supposed to like
you're supposed to. So, it goes
and Alexander, don't disrespect
on your panel. No. Well, I
know. I'm friends with them.
Oh, so I gotta be your friend
to disrespect. Oh, okay.
What? You're just expecting me
No, but I'm not gay. You're not
Put an end on me. You know
Go be gay go be gay go be gay with
Go be gay with clumsy a dog
Kate imagine imagine being friends with people that Docs that doc your kid, right?
Okay, never forget Kate you shared big T's kid school information, then you try to be friends with her yikes imagine that Kate yikes
Don't talk about family members though. Yikes Kate. I'm on your ass. I'll go load this war Kate the word about me
word by elbow and big C Kate
ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring
So fuck nigga take on on a girl you ugly bitch go get dick
Go get dick bitch you ugly disgusting
piece of shit
Imagine you got a you talk about worms in the ass while you got a rash on your ass
You ugly fuck. I never seen a bitch pay 8k on a nigga and still get no buns
I'm obsessed you you talking about me, so I'm giving you the attention
You desperate bitch. You're desperate. You still don't get the action
Desperate bitch
All that shit y'all talk about Vicky y'all over there by Vicky too
Fuck out of here nigga. Stay by stay by sharing and stay by sight nigga
Do you just call me the n-word? I'm not talking to you
Mind your business site
Well, you go kick me if you're rooting me
Well, I'm rude to you psych. I'm sorry, man. It's like you're grown-ass man. I'm sorry. I'm so rude to you
Yeah, it's called it's called the quorum. You haven't heard the core. I'm sorry
I'm sorry psych. I'm sorry
Shut up site you start getting emotional
I'm not emotional. Oh, that's mouth. Oh, that's mouth
Fuck that's not that bro. Yo bring scum me on panel
No, no, what yo bring scum me on panel
Like that, so drop the link for scum me. I'm tired of his ass, too
You could tell that shit stink nigga
Blow that shit somewhere else blow that shit somewhere else. Hey, you like this. No, I'm gonna crash out. I'm crashing out
See you force me to crash out. Do it right now. What? I want to see you. I want to see you crash out. It's hot
What's that? What's what?
I want to see it. Show me
Show me everything
So I took a fort for it, Vanna.
You didn't hear nothing.
Same as you did in the show, he did.
Vanna, you didn't hear nothing, Vanna.
You didn't hear nothing, Vanna.
That wasn't no, though.
And Vanna, there's no proof.
Show clip, show clip.
It's disgusting.
Show clip, Vanna.
There's no clip or nothing.
Who was in number?
Who was up here?
I see nobody in chat.
AI clip, there's more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
If you're a girl I came up to you. Can you came up for me?
Hit me in the IG I came up to you and I sent you pictures I came up for me to I
And I give you that wonderful smile you're oh that wonderful smell. Yeah, it's mouth
Not smell. I think you smell crazy. Not a wonderful smell
Come on. I'm about to be out. I'm out of here. I'm team Dita. Okay. I want it. I want to cook
No, look, you know, how do you know that mouse wasn't eating a rat poison?
I don't know.
That's why I'm not going to give it to my, um, I suppose from the Petco.
So it's probably,
I'm talking about the mouse.
The wild mouse.
They be cats.
Well, you know, I just hope they don't.
They don't.
How do you think Petco could give you poison in his mouse?
No, that's really good.
I don't know.
I mean, it's like, if I could take the mouse.
Have you ever tried to take food out of a hungry, you know, you know, baby's mouth?
They, um, it's called taking candy from babies and it's not appropriate.
So, there, nothing vacant, there, no, there's the, uh, there you go, oh yeah, you like that.
It's called slow death, Yu-Gi-Oh master, don't fuck, oh, I've seen cats eat poison in his
mouth and die plenty of times, eat poison in a rat's over here.
Okay, go away Simon. What are you kicking me out? What are we having a conversation you're gonna leave and then
Well, I'm waiting for scum a you fucking well scum a well I take 20 minutes to get up here
You know I'm gonna eat your bacon that bacon eat that pork. I'm Muslim
There you go. I ain't Muslim though. There you go.
That's the hammer. That's hammer. That's that's that's the hammer. I know. I didn't know hammer was Jewish. Oh, hell yeah. Oh, I know. Yeah, that can't look sick. Yeah. Yeah. Something wrong with oh my god. Well, it's okay kitty. Don't feed it bacon.
What would you feed the bacon out of here?
You should change it to this
Yo, fuck you bitch ass nigga. Well, you are the n-word my brother
White brother
You are white, you know that the British or the
Dominicans or Spanish colonized
New York or wherever island your family comes from you are white sir stop saying
the word and just do what this picture tells you to
It's the only time the mask full of
That's when I breathe
When the static becomes on
I'm honey on your sins
Then I'm all you're told
My name is
I believe
What are you gonna do about it huh huh
What do you need to do about it?
Inward with an A
Tommy James
All right. No, shut up. Hey guys. Hey guys. Hey go with a H
Oh
Well, what you like
Well, what's wrong with you? What's up with you? What's up with you? Well, your girl not
Your girl not wiping your ass no more you got the mud
Wow, you don't even wipe your ass like
How do you know we've seen you like you want to show your body
No
You want some
in a
A very offensive way, but I'm on the floor
Closeted you in the closet you piss on the floor though. You're in the closet are Kelly
What
I thought you was blind, but you're playing you playing I'm not you're playing fight night
Oh, you were you blind by playing for tonight?
You can fart night. I don't play that you play that
You watch it playing for a night. Oh, I'm blind. I'm playing for a night and I'm
Blind I play for tonight. Yeah, you can see that's a script
Also, that's in screed shadows. That was a script. That was the script you should
You should check out my streams on my channel
Scumming you should try it. You should try making a video check out my streams
You trying to make it look normal. I've got to be able to play video games
You trying to make yourself look normal
The Lord the
You don't believe in the Lord or the dark Lord or many gods whatever fucking religion you follow
Sam and
Satanism
What fucking Scientology, whatever fucking shit
You praise white men only right white men on
I respect the money but I respect the money. You beg for
careful. Respect the money. Give me my back boy. You beg
for my dollar back. Give me careful. No, give me my dollar
back. So, I don't make it here.
Here, I'm gonna do something to make you jealous. What? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, do a jumping jacks and make me jealous
Yeah, and you might you might get jealous. Yeah
Unless you buy him from what?
Look, he's happy you want to do it over here. Look. Look. Yeah. MS 13 or do you buy it from other terrorist groups?
Let me sign up. You sound like a cop, man. I
Am a cop nigger
Whoa
No
Wow, why are you being racist?
Yeah, that's I don't feel sorry for you
You a clown you a clown
No, you are Mark as Buster. Yeah. Hope you get hopped on you. I'll destroy you
You'll you'll clown in the circus. I'll destroy you, bro
Even I'll just ride in the city of New York. I live in New York City crime. Oh
Do you actually fuck your girl?
Because ain't no way you fucked your girl.
Let's go outside.
You know what you're getting at, baby?
See, then go outside.
Your girl is wiping your ass again.
Fuck.
Hey, open your window right now, man.
You're going to get fucked by that.
Let's hear your audio.
That's what you hate.
You hate black guys.
Fuck it.
Your girl is fucking at me.
So he hates black guys.
He hates black guys.
I can't imagine.
I love black guys.
Yeah, okay, I can't imagine you get up there. Yeah, you know what I love you same man. What I actually I love
Eldo, he's a black guy. I believe he's black. You're not black
You want big dig now?
Tell your girl saving for your girl, man. See you're gonna watch
Wanna watch a very good fuck, but not you Sam and you're too white
Would you watch your girl get fucked right potty turn you on
You got way into that diddy trial
She looked like she looked like she looked like she don't wash up. What's great. What's great?
She's like one true. Well, I see her camera
You saw her on camera. Where did you see her on camera when you showed up when you showed your house
You're doing creepy shit behind.
No, you showed your house.
You showed your house when you do ericus sneakers.
I'm going to find you and I'm going to kill you one day.
And I'm going to get you in the head.
And when I find you, you're not going to know who I am.
She's a biggie.
She a biggie.
Ain't no one with a biggie.
I like them thick, but she needs to watch her eyes.
She needs to watch her eyes.
Bodies of old women.
Damn
That's how your girl need to watch I like
Is I will take up your mother's bones and grind them up and
smoke them in a fucking crack pipe
Yeah, you know what I do that. I'd shoot up her fucking ashes. I think you too. You did too many
Dead
Family members that's taking there's power
I didn't even do that sight that was him don't blame me so go ahead and back up. Yeah, let him back up
He crashed it now land back up and crashed out
Hello, ma'am crash out man. Yeah, I don't know. He's not he's saying stuff that it's against you
No, no, it's not just deleted. Yeah, it is against us to like make threats against people's family members city and we're
No, it's not. No. Yeah. Where's the end word is bad. Yeah, the hard R. Yes, dude. That's that's yeah
That's that's enough to kick him off
Give him one more chance. We see what he's talking about. You know, he's like, so he's just laughing backstage
He's laughing. Let's see. Let's see. Put him back. Put him back about channel
Look, he looked like a ape. Look, he apes you. Look, he looks crazy.
He doesn't care about your channel, dude.
He doesn't care. He wants you to lose your channel.
You don't want disrespecting it?
I'm not saying nothing.
No, I disrespected the channel because I have brain injury, dude.
Wow, now he's using that as an excuse.
No, I have no filter.
So what you doing? So how you treat your wife?
Do you treat your wife like that?
No.
You sure cuz I heard you scream at her plenty of times. Oh really scream for her or scream at her
At her I'll take that back at her. Oh cuz cuz when she brings me sandwiches and I know you said fuck out of your sandwich
No, no, you scream at oh, yeah, no, you scream at her. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
And I say, what's up, man?
Yo, what's your ass, what's your ass, right?
What's your ass, bro?
What the hell you saying?
When I told you, I kill her every night.
Wow, Minecraft.
And you go, oh my god, call the cops,
get a welfare check.
I didn't say that, people in the L were saying this.
Different not a comedian. You're not a comedian. Are you are you from tough ass, New York?
Are you gonna?
Where park and brain injury in the fucking morning and my car
Yeah, me if you're fucking hard. I've had I've had
Too many friends die from nigger fucking drug dealers like minecraft
No, in real life in my crowd
respect the panel
Yeah, I don't like that
Well, I'm crash out man. Oh, I'm not letting him crash out and it brings a danger to my show
I can't I don't like that. So it's like you ain't gonna keep this up. Anyway, stop talking about gets it up for a year
It's longer than you kept kept the channel up. No, no, I'm talking about damn. What I kept channels. What I never lost a channel site
I'm talking about the live site. Well, I know I probably will keep the live. I can edit them. Yeah, just edit it out
Let him crash out. We need a morning crash. I'll give what the people want the people want the content
I don't feel like letting him crash out on my show because it's dangerous in my show
Yeah, but you can always delete it if it goes too far. Just delete it already gone too far
Do you hear me? I'm deciding who I want on my show or not. I don't want them on the show
Why are you yelling at me? They keep insisting like it's like no, I'm running my show
I'm not gonna tell you who to have in your show and what
I'm just saying that the chat want the ones in the chat y'all once got made back. I don't care
My show I get to find a decision, right? I ain't gonna laugh. It's too early to go live
Yeah, well, I'm doing why you yelling at me? What?
Why are you getting so aggressive with me, huh?
I don't like when you get aggressive for me man. I don't like you ain't get aggressive for me. All right, so stop being stop being aggressive for me
Stop being aggressive though. Only only ladies to be aggressive like out. Get the fuck out then
You sound like a um, you know what you sound like
You're very careful
Hey, bitch, how about that about
It was not nice having on the show and go fuck yourself
So if you want to be mad at whoever, you can't watch though, well, oh, I missed it, you missed
it.
Just this idiot named Scum came in saying much stupid shit.
Oh, that's you, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Good Lord
Next time I'm here
I'm not fragile, I'm forced
I don't fall, I transform you
On the phone the way through
They love you when you're youthful
Hate you when you're free
Wanna save you're on a leash
Not a man with the keys
I wanna show you, just go to this website.
Hold on, I'm gonna show you another one.
Go get your fortune at this website, have fun.
Well, it's free.
Go there.
Black ass, uh-oh, bodega weed.
No
Anyone bugs me and my cats
Automatic kicked out there you go
Go go test it out. You can also see I'll see the preview of the psyche first. Oh, that's like that's not ready yet
Okay, but that one's ready. This one's pretty much ready
Check it out. Yeah, they're free right now. They're free. It's just an oracle. It's a and so it'll be one of ten goddesses
They're really cool and there's a lot of other stuff to that. There's a lot of extras like a lot of like little rituals and
Other practices and a lot of information and you can learn and and get a reading and it's all it's all fun
It's all fun. It's all good. Actually, I think you probably be impressed with the
Stuff I'll put out. I think it's pretty cool
There's no there's no psyche. Yeah, get a little Norse sweatshirt. They're going to $45
Let's see, what is your see your profile name is 66 route 66, but
It's gonna thinks he's so like clever or something like that. He thinks he's being like so edgy or school or something
That's kind of just lame. Oh
Yeah, no, I'll do real readings too
No, I'm not clicking anything. I'm not clicking anything
Dave Chappelle equals black ass
Stargazer see
No, it wasn't true like what happened is I lost my channel for a few weeks and then when I came back there's everyone unmodded and
So
It's good for me one of the things
That wasn't true, I don't know I don't people spread rumors and stuff like that on this community, you know
I know you're a good model.
If you'd like to be a model, you may be a model.
Absolutely.
I was actually looking and trying to find you
because I, yeah, I mean, I'll do readings,
but nobody even asks.
I mean, people ask that I'll do them,
or, you know, I don't, I haven't even like really,
you know, it seems like I've been slandered so much,
like nobody really even wants a reading from me,
so it's fine, you know?
I'm not gonna, I like wait for the invitation
rather than like, you know, try to like,
Force anything on anybody, but if you know try out and try out the Oracle I made though
That's really pretty cool, and it's free and no obligation. You might like it better than you like me
Would you like a card? Hey, man, I got cards
Use my food cards here
It has a little, it has a cute little book to it too.
Can't decide what to eat, but the universe decide for you.
Okay, maybe that's, maybe it will help you decide
what to eat, maybe it will have a great message to it.
I think it'll probably have a good message to it.
These are a little bit different cards, you know?
So I might have to like look it up, but.
You got the orange one.
Okay, there's the orange, oh no, let me put
this full screen for you, I'm so sorry.
Let me see.
There we go.
The orange one, okay. It looks like a salsa. It looks like a nice spicy orange salsa, you know.
What is that? Or it looks like some kind of like middle eastern food. Oh, it's British,
so it's probably a shepherd's pie. Shepherd's pie, it's a little bit orange sometimes because
they have these mashed potatoes they mix with a little bit of like a red sauce, but let me see.
So the orange one, let's see what that is.
Actually, this doesn't have very good descriptions of them, but a perfect blend so I guess you're supposed to like maybe I'll pull three
You're supposed to see what will go with that dish, right? This is like a weird. We're we're deck. It's full food. Oh
Split okay, maybe splitting something with somebody
It's a banana split, okay?
Got orange, maybe like some kind of like orange caramel sauce on top of that. That'd be good and then a split
What does it mean what message? Okay. Well the orange one is like a shepherds pie. Okay, so it's me making a pie sharing it with somebody
What else we got
And then we have greens make sure you have a side of vegetables. Maybe that's money or something like that coming for you
Okay, maybe you're gonna bake something
share the recipe share something about it with somebody and then
You got the greens, of course I have a green screen, so it's coming out purple and stuff like that, right?
How did these work? These are the food fortunes, okay?
It says soon after the deck was created, okay, let me see
Because it has like a lot of these ways to play it says the simplest of all methods shuffle the deck draw one card
Here's what is on the one card. Did you draw the sweet holy one? Congrats. You're having donuts for dinner
You draw a drink even though you're starving
How does that make you feel?
The satisfied, draw another.
Hey, I think maybe some orange chicken
with like a little bit of spinach, right?
This is just to help you decide what to eat for the night.
But it can mean other things to you.
There's a split involved, there's a pie,
a shepherd's pie maybe, and there's a greens, right?
Okay, anybody else want a card?
I know this is kind of a weird deck,
it's a little bit odd, okay, you know.
I'm gonna pull this up for a general for the chat.
Ooh, we have the Blanco dip, we have a white dip.
Okay, there's a delicious white dip, okay?
What does that mean?
It's like something to share, a good appetizer, you know?
Some to share something with somebody, share the wealth,
share, you know, be generous this holiday season,
get some gifts for everybody that you can, you know?
Share, love this holiday season.
I think that's a good message, right?
Yeah, I'm not sure how these exactly correspond to like the normal cards. They're just cute
I think they're really cute cards the white dip. Hopefully that doesn't refer to like me, but no, I'm just kidding. No, I'm not
Hey, hey, baby, so we put these down
Okay. Oh, hi, baby. Hi, baby. Oh, I
Just called the Chad dips. Oh, I didn't mean to you just just just blame it on me. Just call me
Oh, that's mr. Tricks. Hey Tricks
Hi.
Oh, Trix, do you like being rubbed?
Do you like being rubbed?
Yes.
Oh, you like being rubbed.
Oh, how about your ear like that?
Your ear like that.
How about me?
Oh, go in your ear.
Go in your ear.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
And there's Rudy back here.
Rudy wants attention too.
Hi.
Rudy has like a little meow.
He goes, wow.
You know like the food cards. Yeah, we're all out of white dips
I don't know they got like you know if I would like to do like a long reading and stuff for somebody, but it's like
you know
It does take a little bit of energy. I'm a little bit sick right now and
You know I
Need to be specially requested by a particular person
To do that you're a bunch of white dips. Yeah
Well dip dip in what hey, you know, I like dips. I like dips because you know dips are a blend
It's maybe it's also blending some of the cultures blending family
And sharing with every you know making sure you're everyone is everyone is taking care of and
You know it's a nice can be cheesy it can be it can the white dip probably has some like, you know, white sauce in it
Wait, but best you know a
Nice sit up like a white cheddar cheese sounds delicious, right? Mmm. I'm getting hungry. Hi also Santa Claus
I don't know why I thought of that Santa Claus. I just thought you know, he likes that
You know, these will dip out for Santa this year instead of a cookie. Hey, babe. Oh, hi, babe
I'm gonna cuddle with me. Oh, you're rubbing against me. Hey. Well, I
Love my kitty cats
Yeah
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm a little bit out of sorts and character like recently
It's just like a lot of stress
Like I said a lot of misunderstandings and I hate misunderstandings I hate like
Miscommunication especially with like people I love because it's like now. There's like almost like too late to fix it
you know probably
Takes two people, you know to want to fix it and you know
Yeah, somebody doesn't want it. It's like you can't force anybody to do anything, you know
There you want to you know, you want it to be the person, you know, everyone wants to do it
Unfortunately
Like I said, I'm pretty easy to to throw away so
You know, but I do say there wasn't a center standing and you know, I would always appreciate another chance, but
You know that's not up to me
Anyway, thanks for being in between this morning. I hope you have a good nice day guys. Love you. Have a nice day